I'm sorry, my network seems to be off again, so I'll do it again.
Hello everyone, I'm Aivie, a designer from CLO.
Welcome to the first live broadcast of CLO's Bilibili.
If you have any questions during the live broadcast, you can send them through the chat.
If you can answer them in text, we will answer them in text online.
If you need to hide something, we will also select some questions in the Q&A section at the end to answer.
If there is no way to send a chat or there is no time to ask a question,
you can also follow our WeChat official account to leave a message.
You can scan the QR code on the picture directly,
or scan the QR code in the lower right corner of the screen
to pay attention to the message.
When the live broadcast video is released,
we will open a live broadcast in WeChat official account.
The prize of the event we set this time is very rich.
The highest prize is about 10,000 yuan.
I hope everyone can participate.
Our live broadcast this time is divided into four parts.
The first one is what is CLO.
The other is how to make clothes in CLO.
And our cooperative platform CLO SET.
What are the advantages of CLO in the business?
If you have any questions, you can try to answer them online.
Because of my internet speed, there may be a little bit of a problem here.
If you have any delays or later problems,
I hope everyone can just take it as our network is more naughty.
First of all, let's talk about what is CLO.
Our CLO's name is CLO Virtual Fashion.
We are in Seoul, South Korea.
There are two products in the following.
One is CLO 3D, the other is Marvel Designers.
There are a total of six branches in the world.
We mainly focus on 3D fashion and psychological technology to demonstrate B-Cell 5D.
Like the fold on this coat.
A sleeves of a waistband.
A fine line of the shoulders.
The effect of the face of the dress.
Including the internal structure of its face.
Multi-layer fashion.
clothes, layers, clothing, cut, color matching, and other details can be expressed very well in CLO.
In addition to making clothes, we can also make accessories such as bags, gloves, etc. in CLO.
We can see the details of different parts through different perspectives.
We can also present our clothes to customers through 360 video methods.
We can also open the clothes and check the details of the clothes through 360 video.
Just like this jacket, we can open it to see the details of the clothes inside.
Next, let's take a quick look at how to make clothes in CLO.
After the sheet is poured in, we can simulate it.
After the clothes are worn, we can use the corresponding fabric to check the effect of the clothes.
Now we are going to change it.
We can change it to a skirt, lengthen it, or shorten it.
Then we will make a elastic band on the waist and make a cut to it.
We can use different fabrics.
When it comes to the sleeves, we can also make a cut.
We can also use a lace on the sleeves.
We can also make a slit in the middle.
This is the effect of the sling.
Finally, let's improve the quality of clothing.
We can see the final clothing form through the rendering.
This is the final effect.
We can see that this is very realistic.
We CLO can also present 3D clothing to everyone through the show.
We can show 3D clothing to everyone through the show.
We can also suit the model.
We can choose the corresponding motion and see the final clothes in the software.
The effect of different clothing and the performance of the show is also significantly different.
Take this dress for example.
It is relatively thin.
It looks a little flamboyant.
If it is a bit more valuable, it will not have the feeling of flamboyant.
The words are the same, it is also relatively light.
Like this set, this is a set of clothes.
When you walk in the show, you can also see the effect of a set of clothes on the clothes.
You can see that when you walk in the show, the clothes follow some changes in the model's posture.
There will be some changes in the shape.
Now we will integrate many sets of clothes together to walk in the show.
It feels very much like we are in the real world to watch the show.
And we can take a look at different details from different angles.
Next, we will directly operate how to make a piece of clothing in CLO.
First, we open this software.
Then we first load a virtual model.
Then we import the DXF version.
Click the
After that, we first use the positioning ball to properly arrange the location of this front piece in 3D.
Then we go to the overall arrangement, open the arrangement point.
Then we can click this piece of board and click this arrangement point.
This version will quickly be wrapped around the model
Let's arrange this sleeve
Let's arrange this back piece
After that
We turn off the arrangement
Next, sew
Our sewing
It can be done in 3D
It can also be done in 2D
Now let's sew this back middle
Sew the sleeve, sew the bottom seam
Sew the sleeve
Then you can see that each sewing line
We only need to press once or twice to complete
And the color of each sewing line is different
That's mainly because of its color
Is produced randomly
So it's a little different
Okay, let's take a look at this front part
First of all, here
We don't choose at the beginning
This sewing method
We choose to use the buttoning method
To close it
We can increase the buttoning on the board
Then we quickly
The button is also copied to a symmetrical board
Then we use the thin buttoning tool
Tighten this button
Then now we can open the simulation
Then we can also simulate the human hand in the real world
A way to move the clothes
To move our 3D clothing
Next, let's take a look at this buttoning in this computer editor
Then we can choose different buttoning patterns
Different types
After changing, it will change here
Then let's take a look at this width
We can change it a little bit
Then let's change its type
You can choose metal or plastic, etc.
All right
Then let's change its color
Now let's take a look at this buttoning
That's the buttoning with the buttoning
Let's change its width
Let's change its color at the end
This is now the same thing
But the key is still the same
Then we can change it
Continue the same way
The color seeped in
Then we can go back to our home
that's a buttoning
It's like this
This is a buttoning and a buttoning
It's a way to close it in front
Now we're going to remove the buttoning and the buttoning
Let's get rid of it
Let's choose another way to close it in front
Then we choose this zipper
Then this tool is in the back
Let's move it a little bit
We choose this zipper tool
In the front, add one number
After adding a zipper, we will click on the simulation, and we will find that the front and back are also closed.
After closing, we can select the zipper and pull it down.
Click on the simulation again and you will find that the upper part is open.
This is a functional zipper display.
In the manual editor, we can change the zipper zipper and its zipper.
And we can change its type, which is the same as the button just now.
For example, let's change it to metal and then change its color.
This is the zipper.
Next, let's talk about the zipper.
For the zipper, you can also change its width.
I won't change it here.
Then let's take a look at the texture part.
We only provide two in the software.
You can also add your own texture.
OK.
This is the zipper.
Finally, we pull the zipper up.
Then we simulate it again and it closes again.
Then we delete the zipper.
Finally, we use the sewing method to close the front and back.
These are the three ways to close the zipper.
OK.
Next, let's change the board.
Before changing the board, we first make the side line straight.
We make it straight.
After that, it'll look like this.
We make it longer.
Once it's yelling straight, it makes it look longer up and down.
Things like this.
After that, we make this thimble.
OK.
That's it.
Soon it'll look like this can be seen.
Then you push it forward.
It'll be cut open.
We turn it over.
Can pass through here.
What is this?
It's vertical.
It's horizontal.
It'sταν.
So we turn it over and open like this.
like this.
You can see it's horizontal.
OK.
I'm going to call it like this.
Yes, next.
It's a vertical one.
This is a vertical.
You see the teacher table.
Theっていう.
There's a superior table in here.
It's getting longer and wider.
Next, we're going to add an elastic band effect to the waist.
First, we're going to hook it up into an inner line.
Then we're going to add another inner line on the basis of this inner line
to simulate the upper and lower two ropes of this elastic band.
Next, we're going to add an inner line.
We're going to open this elastic band in the right side of the attribute editor
and then open the opening simulation.
You'll find that this dress is closed.
And we can adjust the proportion to see the different effects of the elastic band.
You can adjust it to be loose or tight.
This is the elastic band's performance.
Next, we're going to adjust the sleeve.
We're going to shorten the sleeve.
And we're going to change the outline of the outer sleeve.
Next, we're going to...
Next, we're going to change the outline of the outer sleeve.
We're going to adjust the outline of the outer sleeve.
You can do some small details on the sleeves.
For example, I'm going to add two stiches.
Before adding a stich, we add two points on the outer cross-stitch.
After adding it, we use this stich as the center to add an index.
Another point is also done the same operation.
This is the change of the sleeves.
Next, let's make a collar for the skirt.
We don't make a five-collar.
We make a small plate as its collar.
First, draw a curved plate.
Then we sew it.
If you don't have a registered or unregistered comment,
you can follow our WeChat account in the lower right corner.
Follow our WeChat official account and leave a message.
This is the collar.
Let's rearrange the collar.
OK.
The collar is finished.
Next, we can make a change to the plate in 3D.
Let's make some cuts to the collar.
You may think that these two points are not symmetrical.
I choose randomly.
If you want to be symmetrical, you can choose the plus point tool.
Then cut it off.
After cutting it off,
you can choose this plate in 2D or 3D.
You can delete it.
Then you can do the simulation again.
You can see that now it has a slight collar effect.
It's a hollow collar effect.
Then we merge the front and the front.
Then we also merge the back.
After merging,
we can add a sticker to the 3D.
We can add a sticker to the 3D.
This is the sticker.
In order to make the stickers easier to add,
we can hide this model.
It's easy.
All we need is a single click.
When the double click is over at the end,
you can see that the stickers are done.
With the stickers,
we can change its length
and width as we need it.
For example,
as I change its width here to 8,
you can see that it changes clearly.
Then we move the model out of the way, and by this point, our clothes will be finished.
Let's change the pose. Let's change this T-pose to an A-pose and put his arm down.
If you have a card, you may need to refresh it or go back out and refresh it.
Okay, this is our pose.
Next, we will add some fabric for this dress.
You know that different fabrics have different shapes on the same dress.
First, let's add a leather. Look at it. It's harder. This dress is stopped.
Next, let's add a snow-covered fabric.
Let's simulate it again. You can see that it's loosened.
The snow-covered fabric is softer, not as hard as the leather.
Finally, let's add a more straight fabric.
Okay.
It's a cotton jersey.
Then let's simulate it again.
Okay. Next, let's add a pattern.
After adding the pattern, we can edit the pattern in 3D or 2D.
You can zoom in, zoom out, rotate, etc.
You can also move the pattern on the same board.
On the same board, not on the same board.
Look at it again.
Because you need to move the pattern on the same board.
It's like a pattern.
Look at it again.
Here is the pattern, and look at the pattern again.
And you can see it.
It's all nice and natural.
If you look at it in 3D.
Look at it again.
Then you can see it like this.
Look at the pattern.
As you see it.
Next, let's add some small details.
For example, let's add a name line.
Let's add a name line at the bottom.
You can see that this name line has been added.
Then we hope that this name line
can be changed in the place where the seal is pasted.
Then we can also choose a different type of name line.
Then we don't change it here.
The auto-generated type of name line is fine.
Then we choose its roughness and then change its color.
We can use the straw tool to quickly extract a color
that matches the sound.
Then we also add a name line
in the place of the sleeve.
We can copy this name line
and copy it out in the computer editor on the right.
Then add this name line on the sleeve.
The type of this name line is unchanged.
We just need to change it.
We just need it to be a little closer to the outline.
So let's change its diameter to 1.
Then we can 3D print it and see the effect.
It has an obvious pressure effect.
This is an addition of some small details
to this dress.
Finally, let's pick one to improve the quality of the clothes.
In order to perform some more delicate clothing folds,
we all need to improve the quality of the clothes.
Then let's open the simulation again.
You can see that the clothes are slowly folded.
The feeling is very real.
It's different from the first time we wore it.
The effect is different.
This is an improvement to the quality of the clothes.
If the quality of the clothes are not well maintained,
it will affect the overall quality of the clothes.
So I'll add the last line to this model.
After the quality is improved,
we'll draw the front waist.
There is a crook,
right?
We hope to draw a small butterfly on its front waist.
The butterfly has two belts.
So I'll draw two auxiliary lines first.
让我扎个腰带啊,我现在已经在扎腰带了啊,然后我们现在来添加这个蝴蝶结进来。
那添加这个蝴蝶结进来之后呢,我们就要对它进行一个缝合啊。
缝合完之后呢,我们对它进行一个模拟。
现在我们这个开启一下这个模拟,看一下。
然后可以看一下,那这就是一个腰部松紧带,然后添加了一个蝴蝶结。
那我的操作可能有些快啊,因为我本人现在还是前面由于网络的问题,现在本人还是有一些紧张。
好。
把这个内部线隐藏掉,我们现在来看一下这个起色啊。
那在哦面同样一件衣服呢,可能有很多个颜色嘛,对吧。
那在我们同样一件衣服呢,可能有很多个颜色嘛,对吧。
那再说这件衣服裙子的话,比如说我们来换一个纹理来看一下它的效果。
再说这件衣服裙子的话,比如说我们来换一个纹理来看一下它的效果。
看一下不同的印花在同样一件衣服上的一个效果。
比如说我们来换一个其他的纹理。
那可以看一下那它的纹理马上就变了。
its texture will change immediately.
After the texture changes, the color will not be the previous yellow.
Then we also have to change the color of the thread.
Use the straw tool to adjust it a little bit.
So that the color of the thread can distinguish the color of the fabric.
Then we click on this update.
Now you can see that there are two colors in this dress.
Then let's go back to this flower arrangement mode.
In this mode,
we can adjust the pattern of this fabric.
First, we can make this door frame a little wider.
Then we want to re-arrange this.
You want to see how to use this pattern.
You can drag this board to adjust its position.
We hope that the bottom of these two boards are aligned,
so we will choose to align its bottom.
Then we can re-adjust the sleeves.
We can see that
we are also able to adjust the hemline.
The hemline is a little bit of a problem.
So I'm going to adjust it a little bit.
the width of the door and the height of the door are all variable.
Then it can roughly estimate how much material is used to make such a dress.
This is one of the functions of the hard flower arrangement mode.
Finally, we return to the simulation mode.
This dress is basically done here.
Next, we will make a combination.
Because this dress is relatively large, so I will make this dress a little tighter.
We all know that if you wear a loose dress and a tight dress,
it must be a tight dress that is easier to match.
So we will first change this dress in the way of shrinkage.
In the same way, we also need to make the edges tighter.
We choose this edge to make it a little tighter according to the same method of shrinkage.
Then we will simulate it again.
You can see that this dress is tighter than the one just worn.
It's not that loose.
In order for us to wear it, we need to make it a little tighter than the one just worn.
Then we will make it a little tighter than the one just worn.
It's easier to match clothes, and it's easier to wear a jacket.
Then we choose these pieces again.
We will make the shrinkage a little tighter.
We change it to 80.
Then we change the edges of the dress.
Then we simulate it again.
You can see that it is tighter.
You can clearly see that the hollowed out neck is the same as the one just worn.
You can see that the hollowed out neck is the same as the one just worn.
Due to the tighter nose and clothes space, the parts of the collar can be a bit open than the first size.
You may see a kn잣
Then we make the cover in the middle of color and cross on the length of another fabric.
We make the cover in the middle of color and cross on the length of another fabric.
After that, we change its level to 1, which means that it is on the top of the clothes inside, so when it is simulated again, you will find that the clothes are worn on the outside of the skirt inside, and such a dress is done.
Then we change this level to 0 at the end, because the original glow rate is not its original color, and then we change it to a shrink rate, and then change it back to 90, because the reason why I changed the shrink rate in advance is mainly because I want to put this coat on.
Now, after the coat is on, the clothes inside still have to be restored to the beginning.
We can't just do it.
We have to change the shape of a dress.
Then we slowly change it to 100.
Then we simulate it.
When we simulate it, we find that the bottom of this dress may have some shapes, some are not very beautiful, not very good-looking.
Then we slowly change it to 100.
Then we tool the design a little, so that we can evaluate its principles.
You might watch my video too fast, because I speak fast.
You don't have to worry that we havemportant quality.
There will be a video release later, and there will be a pre-seasoning event.
Then this suit will be done.
Now let's see the not Literal ي
This is a 3D costume.
It's going to be a very good performance.
This will be replayed.
Because of the time,
we can directly show you this rendering picture here.
Because rendering is more time-consuming.
This is the most important picture effect.
Then we make a good costume file.
You can use our Closet platform for information interaction.
After we log in to Closet,
we can create a company, brand, product line, and workshop on this platform.
After creating a workshop,
we can upload 3D files according to our needs.
After uploading, we can upload it.
We can share it to others by email.
And we can set other people's
to watch the whole line.
After receiving this email,
you can click on this link to log in to this Closet platform.
We can watch this clothes online.
You can see this clothes.
It has a color.
You can also switch to check.
And you can zoom in on it.
You can hide the model and check some of the inside effects.
And you can make some postage or back up.
Or make some suggestions to modify.
In addition, we can also download a process list on this platform.
In this process list, you can see the display of four perspectives.
And you can also see the cut-and-paste.
And a pattern of different colors.
And a situation of color use.
Now, I will show you the postage.
After the postage, you have a different color way.
You can check the different colors.
And which color are you using?
Which texture are you using?
And so on.
In this, there will be a table for you to see.
Finally, we will talk about why we use Closet.
Through Closet, we can make 3D clothing.
We can turn grass into a more visual 3D image in advance.
And it can reflect the image.
It can reflect the real pattern, fabric, and even some workmanship.
So, through 3D clothing, we can find some pattern problems earlier.
We can confirm the design earlier.
Reduce the misunderstanding in the communication.
Avoid repeating the real sample.
Reduce the cost of the sample.
It also greatly shortens the response to the market cycle.
On the other hand, because 3D clothing can objectively reflect a lot of information.
So, it can also effectively improve communication efficiency.
By implementing revision functions, it can increase the number of designs.
And it can also increase our choice rate.
In summary, it is that.
Three decreases and three increases.
Reduce the misunderstanding in communication.
Reduce the cost of the sample, and so on.
It increases the communication efficiency.
Increase the number of designs.
Increase the choice rate.
Finally, we will go back to the Q&A section.
In the previous part, you may have said that this is the first time for me to broadcast such a live broadcast.
I am also a little nervous.
I am also nervous, so I speak faster.
Now, let me take a look at this.
There are some questions that everyone mentioned online.
There are some questions that my colleague has already replied to everyone in the background.
Then I can see some other questions.
See if everyone has any questions.
Share.
Now I will answer the people who have been shared.
Can you still see this rendering effect?
There is a question from Jiangshanyanhua.
If you upload the project file, that is, the project file,
After uploading, it can be rendered in the Closet.
But if you upload this rendering image, it can also see this rendering image.
Do you want to render?
You can do it according to your own needs.
If you need rendering, you can also render with Closet.
You don't necessarily have to render with our software.
In fact, you can also use software.
Can you share myículos?
Our
I can show you this plugin.
Let me show you.
Let me show you this plugin.
In this plugin.
We are in this Closet.
There is a hardware and trims in the default file.
In here.
There is a ribbon in it
There are many butterflies in this ribbon
You can just choose it here
I don't have to share it with you
You can do it yourself
Glittering fabric can be made
You can sweep the glitter
Then you can do it yourself
Glittering effect can be done
I'm using it now
Because of the epidemic
I'm at home
This network speed was originally on at 8 o'clock
Then it was delayed to about 10 minutes later
I'm sorry here
Originally, our software has been upgraded to 5.1.482
But due to the network speed
I'm using 5.1.330 now
There are a lot of add-ons in this
Okay
Is it high-end for a computer
For this question
You can enter 3w.close 3d.com
You can search for this computer configuration
The computer configuration is relatively higher
How to restore software usage?
How to return software usage?
这个问题的话软件试用期的话到了之后你可能就需要自己去购买了这个问题的话软件试用期的话到了之后你可能就需要自己去购买了
因为我们每个人的试用只要你是同一台电脑登录的它会试试验你的ip地址吗所以你就每人只能用一个月
人体模特的尺寸可调吗
这个问题人体的模特尺寸是可以调的可以调的那在我们的虚拟模特这里面有一个虚拟模特编辑器啊我们可以打开看一下
那在这个里面呢有这个虚拟模特的尺寸你在这里可以根据你的尺寸表来输入你这个虚拟模特的尺寸调完之后呢它就可以达到你所想要的一个效果
嗯
呃人体模特可以自己自作替换吗
是这样子的如果我们的模特呢因为我们软件支持你是可以用obj格式的也可以用a vt格式的但是如果你是扫描的模特你可能会把它扫描成obj模式
然后呢扫描的obj模式呢你可以在我们软件当中来做一个转换那
同样的也是
In this virtual model, there is a size that can be converted to a virtual model.
You can take it
One of your copied OBJ
Because OBJ, it's white, it's pure white, right?
Maybe it doesn't look very beautiful
Then you can put that model in
Transformed into a model with skin
It might look a little more beautiful
Uh, how to import the fabric
In our software
Our uh, let's take a look at this fabric file
Well, first of all, we can just pull a fabric file
To the bottom of this
Well, you can see that it's on this fabric
It's a part of the fabric
The other one is still a part of a detail
There is one called physics
It's a physical attribute
So uh, how to get to our software
First you need to scan
Then you need to use our
Uh, a fabric measuring device
A tool like this
To measure its physical properties
And then take it
Uh, from
Put your data into our software
It will become a 3D fabric file
And then you can apply it to 3D clothing
Uh, the next one is how to operate the hollow fabric
Uh, I don't know what you're talking about
Is the hollow fabric the lace fabric?
Like the front
When we do a quick demonstration for you
You'll find that the fabric is a hollow one
We can show you
Uh, the hollow fabric
First of all, it must be a PNG format
Like lace, it's all a PNG format, right
Let's take a look at this lace fabric
Let's see where it is
Let's see if it is the mini-wrap
For example, we switch the volume off
Let's see this hollow fabric
For example, we change the volume
Then you can see that I now made this dress into a hollow.
Originally, you can't see the color inside on the side, right?
You made a hollow fabric, which is this lace fabric.
Its format is PNG format, so you can see it inside.
I don't know if you're talking about this kind of hollow.
Do you need another download for the walk-through scene?
The walk-through scene is in our version.
After 5.1 and 5.1, there are five stages in the back.
You can see that there are some stages in this folder.
This is our walk-through scene.
OK.
Of course, you can also build it yourself.
For example, you can import an OBJ into it as a scene.
We just provide some scenes for everyone to choose from.
When everyone is doing it, you can take a look.
After the model is finished with the walk-through,
it will be more beautiful in such a scene, right?
Can I put a code?
Yes, you can put a code.
In our software, there is a function to put a code.
There is a code here.
How to add the second piece of clothing?
Adding the second piece of clothing.
The operation I just did may be a little fast.
Plus, I'm a little nervous.
Then,
every time we make clothes,
for example,
the clothes we made earlier,
when we make the matching,
we first make one piece of clothing,
then make another piece of clothing,
and then put two pieces of clothing together.
When we make it,
after making one piece of clothing,
we will put that piece of clothing in the software.
Then the other piece of clothing,
we will choose the way to add,
add it in.
In this way, it will be made into a dress.
I don't know if it means this.
How to draw two layers of fabric in a dress?
I'll talk about it again.
I just talked about wearing a dress.
There are no two models for wearing a dress.
But the premise of wearing a dress,
you'd better be the same model,
the same model,
the same posture.
In this way,
it will be faster when you wear a dress.
If you use different models,
it may be different for tall and fat people.
It may be different to wear it.
When you wear a dress,
you may have to do a lot of things.
There are a lot of steps to adjust.
In this way,
the efficiency is not high.
The other one is how to draw two layers of fabric in a dress.
In the case of a dress,
everyone knows that a dress
must have an insomniac.
When we showed it before,
we also talked about the insomniac effect of a dress.
In the inside of the dress,
let's take a look.
Let's take a look at this dress.
Let me show you the effect of this dress.
Because in our dress,
we will choose a way called pressure
to show the insomniac effect.
Let's take a look at this dress.
This is the insomniac effect.
It is the insomniac effect.
Let me demonstrate to everyone
the insomniac effect.
Then you can see that we have a pressure here.
For example, let's change this pressure.
Set the negative value inside and set the positive value outside.
Then we click this simulation to take a look.
Wait a minute.
Let's wait a minute.
It's okay to add a seam allowance.
Wait a minute.
I didn't put it because of the dress in front of me.
How does a model wear make-up?
Probably needs to test your PS technique.
You can go to PS and draw make-up for the model.
For example, give him a lipstick.
You can also draw some eye shadows.
It's okay.
给大家简单看一下这个航红线的一个效果给大家简单看一下这个航红线的一个效果
啊因为我的电脑前面做了一些渲染啊然后开了一天了所以他可能有反应有时候有一点慢
你可以看一下那这个呢他就是基本上一个羽绒服啊呃的一个充棉效果的一个一个一个展示
那你充棉的多少呢就取决于你这个压力值是多少你压力值是越大他充棉效果越明显压力值越小他充棉效果就
不那么明显啊
啊请问可以看回放吗这个问题是可以的就是我们在我们的微信大家可以扫
这个屏幕右下角的这个微信公众号关注一下我们然后呢我们会给到大家一个呃
转发抽抽奖的一个活动前面也讲了吗那我们的价值我们的奖品还是挺丰厚的最高价值是1万块
所以希望大家可以踊跃参与然后呢我们在微信后台发那个
录播视频的时候呢也希望大家多多给我们转发吗
呃
下一次直播是哪些内容是什么时候呃这个的话也我们我现在不能给到具体的答复那具体的话你也可以扫描这个
呃二维码啊然后关注一下我们的微信公众号呃有这个方面的直播消息呢我们都会给到大家
一个一个通知然后大家可以
看一下大家也可以在我们的微信后台进行留言比如说你想要看什么样式呃比如说哪一点的直播比如说呃
怎么样去做一些附近
啊等等啊这些呃
各个要点的一个直播视频那大家都可以去呃提一下自己的意见我们也希望多多收集多多收集大家大家对我们客楼呃各方面的一个建议吗我们也会做一个更好的一个改进啊
啊对我们的价价奖品直播1万还挺还挺高的价价格啊希望大家草苗扫苗这个屏幕下方的二维码参与
呃那个抽奖啊
呃骑色怎么操作呃骑色的话在这里我们的屏幕这边有一个叫右下角有个叫骑色看到吗这个模式啊因为我们的模式呃针对走秀呢我们有动画那针对对花对格以及普通的一个呃嗯一件衣服的一个一个用料情况我们有一个叫印花牌牌料那对于骑色呢我们就有个叫骑色的模式啊
都可以那前面有别人在说面料怎么怎么测啊那这里就有一个叫面料测量的一个这样计算这样一个模式可以把我们的呃实际的一个面料转换成一个三 d 面料就是这样的一个模模式啊
嗯
呃最新版本是5 1 482版本
呃修改的版型之后能导出吗当然可以那我们把这些版片啊我们看一看一下在这个文件啊这边有一个叫导出啊版片dxf你就可以把你所更改在客楼里面所做的一些更改好的版片导出去它同样也是一个dxf版片你可以导到其他的一个cd系统里面去看都可以
呃最开始是导入什么格式的版那我们在最开始导入的时候有一个文件啊导入dxf你可以看到这边是叫aama以及astm两种格式那我们客楼呢目前是只支持dxf格式中的这两种
呃更新软件太卡了我不知道你是我们的客户呢还是说就是民间用户啊那如果是我们的客户的话可以呃跟我们相应的这个技术负责人可以去要一下可能是因为网速的问题更新软件太卡了
那个版片里面画线的工具优化了吗版片里面画线的工具呃这个我不知道具体是什么你可以去到我们的微信公众号留言一下我不大明白这个版片领线画线的工具是什么意思啊
嗯
啊民间用户就是你是私人用的吗你个人在你个人在在用吗可能在用我们的试用版呢可能也是可能是你们购买的个人版
啊你可以登录到我们的官网
那可以到跟我们的官网叫3w.close3d.com你可以去看一下里面啊
里面是有一些试用版的
二地工具里面的褶皱工具还没搞明白是什么意思呃喘坐工具是不是说的这个翻折折剪补的这个
这个叫啊翻折折剪工具啊
那这个呢主要是用来做我们在做多个折剪
时候会用到这个工具那这个呢你可以去我们的官网去搜索一下里面有个
帮助中心你去搜索一下翻折折减那里面会有一个相应的小视频给到
大家一个教学视频呀那在我们的大家很感兴趣的话都可以到我们的
官网里面有很多的教学视频人教学视频大家可以观看
模特怎么穿鞋子啊模特怎么穿鞋子那在我们这个模特里面他是
我们不是自己给他穿鞋子是在我们的设定里面有很多在模特里面在
啊针对每相应的模特就有不同的鞋子可供选择那像在我们我现在用的是
5.1.330版本的话在这个里面就有很多种鞋子吗就有七种鞋子你可供选择
你可能为了搭配
不同的衣服就有需要不同的鞋子对吧
抽奖的话是下周啊下周抽奖
模特的鞋子可以自己做呀也可以自己做的
如何去调整
调整鞋子的颜色啊那鞋子的颜色跟我们调整面料的颜色基本上是一样的就是原理是一样的我们可以选择这个鞋面吗你比如说我把这个颜色去掉它就变成了一个白色那你也可以选择这个颜色啊一开始这个颜色你可以把这个颜色你换一个颜色出来啊
或者是你把它颜色去掉你换到其他颜色去可以换成红的呀你为了匹配自己的这个衣服吗对吧你可以去换它的颜色同样的你可以把它改成
其他种类的有时候改了闪一点你可以改成相应啊或者其他种面料的其他种类型的材质啊都可以
为什么你的就两双你有没有点击这边有一个fabulous这边有一个下载键有一个蓝色的嗯
如果有大家很多的东西没有下载的话那这些东西这些鞋子啊可能一些包括其他的一些前面有人提到的这个
这个蝴蝶结啊等等都没有下载下来
点一下这个下载的箭头把所有的他在云上的呃这个附件啊都下载到这个软件中来那这样子的话你的鞋子就跟我的鞋子是一样了
嗯
那这个看一下这个3 d 背景右键填充啊那你可以子这里不是有两种吗你在三
背景设置里面有两种那第一种呢是以图片或者是纹理填充你可以放一副山水画在这边都可以的那
你说的单纯的用颜色填充的就是这个色块填充啊
做包包类的工艺方便吗那主要看一下你这个包是什么样子的啊如果是比较简单的包的话就前面视频当中前面我们在讲的时候啊会有一个那个包他是有一些金属配件的那个可能稍微做起来稍微麻烦一点那普通的包的话也是比较快的
呃快捷键汇总啊快捷键汇总的话我们是需要我们在官方好像是没有发布这个快捷键
快捷键的会会总那你们可以
自己看一下我们每次把光标放在这个软件上面的时候每个工具上面
像如果他有快捷键的话他在后面都会有一个括号括号里面有一个英文字母那这样子的话就是一个快捷键
额礼布怎么做额一般来说比如说西装的话那他的礼布肯定是有一个面部吗有一个礼布对吧那这样子的话
你就需要去做两层了你做两层的时候呢那你不就是坐在里面面部就是坐在外面那就会那同样一件衣服他就是会有两层两层结构啊
科罗官网找不出
到吗三大不留点科罗三低点看
额我们的软件大家不知道额如果之前有用过我们
5 1之前的版本的话大家应该知道我们的软件现在其实已经汉化挺多的了像之前这个什么模拟呀动画呀这些模式啊都是英文的吗那现在的话
他已经我们也在慢慢的去优化我们的软件这个到目前为止呢优化的目前为止我们的汉化的版本就是五点一点四八二最新版啊五点一点四八二
嗯
额里布的缝合啊里部的缝合
额里布的缝合啊里部的缝合啊
额里布的缝合啊
Let's take a look at it. I'll reset this interface and I'll show you the seam allowance of the lining. I'll use this simple T-shirt to take a look at the seam allowance of the lining with our own T-shirt.
We can see that the T-shirt is just one piece.
We can do the same as we did with the clothes.
For example, we copy the Cologne layer and Cologne V.
When I'm actually making clothes, the lining and the outer layer should be different, right?
The size should be different.
There are some differences.
I'm doing this for quick demonstration.
So I made the lining and the outer layer the same.
For example, the top layer is the lining.
Let's add it to the inside.
The outer layer should be like this.
And we triple it together.
The lining and the outer layer are the same.
The clothing had lined and lining.
There is a seam allowance, and there are temptations of filling them vibrations with lace.
It is for the only time we made match.
I think I did it wrong in the beginning.
So that's the first thing we need to do.
把这个袖子的这些都不要 I don't want any of these sleeves
那这个的话就是里布跟外布的一个缝合啊 Then this is a combination of the inside and the outside.
那这个前面我也讲了这个这个是我就是为了快速的演示给大家看 So I talked about this before. This is what I did to quickly show it to everyone.
所以我是这么一个操作方法 So I am such a way of operation.
那那如果你的版片呢里布肯定是有礼布的版片吗对吧 Well, if your version is the inside, there must be a version of the inside, right?
你这样子往上撩的时候啊你这样往上扯动的时候啊 When you go up like this, when you pull up like this, you can find this version of the inside.
嗯位由于时间的原因呢我们今天的直播到这边啊可能就要结束了 Uh, because of the time, our live broadcast today might be over.
If you have any questions, you can follow our Bilibili account.
You can also follow our Weibo account.
If you don't know our Weibo account, you can follow our WeChat account.
In our WeChat account, there is also our Weibo account and our Bilibili account.
If you have any questions, you can leave a message to us through our WeChat or Weibo or Bilibili.
We also hope that we can optimize it better and better.
Thank you, everyone. Goodbye.